#### Contact

superonecoderman@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/atsushiyamada-132449298 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Back-End Web Development SOAP AngularJS

# Atsushi Yamada

Web and Blockchain Engineer

Okinawa, Japan

## Summary

Computer Science Master candidate actively doing research and development in the blockchain system(Ethereum, Binance, Solana and the other nets) and web production building.

Skillful experiences in NFT minting, NFT marketing platform, NFT gaming system(Metaverse) DAO, DEFI, Dex platforms and smart contracts(using Solidity, Rust, C&C++) for blockchain platforms, integration Web3 on the several blockchain nets as a blockchain developer for 4 years.

## Experience

Upwork

Freelance Developer September 2023 - Present (2 months)

### Opolis

Blockchain FullStack developer July 2022 - September 2023 (1 year 3 months) United States

Experience working with third-party libraries, Geo Toolkit, html2Canvas, Material UI for the frontend development.

Used React JS for templating for faster compilation and developing resuable components.

And also used React JS in components like JSX, creating React components.

Converting StripFan Angular to React + NextJS project (For speed imporvement and to give proper structure)

KodaDot - Creators Marketplace Blockchain FullStack Developer March 2022 - June 2022 (4 months) Made front-end website including token management portal, dashboard, vesting UI using following skills • Developed ERC721, ERC1155, ERC20 smart contracts with solidity and some NFT projects based on EVM.

Crystal Finance

Web3 Frontend PM

June 2021 - February 2022 (9 months)

have worked as a senior web developer and made both frontend and backend. Utilized ReactJS for its efficient data flow architecture to create a lightweight and render efficient web app that searched projects via the GitHub API through keywords.

Developed Restful endpoints with node/express, PHP Frameworks. Integrated web-sockets and web hooks.

Designed and deployed smart contracts for tokens and ICOs including token vesting, refund vaults and multi-signature wallets.

Upwork

Blockchain Freelancer

September 2020 - June 2021 (10 months)

Okinawa, Japan

Worked for almost 2 years as a senior blockchain developer on the upwork site.

Acquired the new skills, abilities and knowledge on this site.

Because there so many developers that acquire the high tech.

**Techverx** 

Full-stack Developer

June 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 4 months)

Worked as a full stack developer and made both frontend and backend. Involved in web application development for back-end system using AngularJS and Node.js with cutting edge Written Web Services using SOAP for sending and getting data from the external interface.

Caktus Group

Frontend Developer

August 2017 - July 2019 (2 years)

Worked on building new React components for the customer-facing web app which improved the time on page.

Worked within an agile team and helped prioritize and scope feature requests to ensure that the biggest impact features were worked on first.

Alchemy

Intern

November 2016 - June 2017 (8 months)

Integrated Stripe payment integration

Supported the DevOps team to automate CI/CD processes

## Education

Okinawa International University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (September 2012 - August 2016)